if you are if you work from the
government turn this off right now and
you can you did not hear anything I just
said anyways what's a translating what
what's a WikiLeaks
[Music]
chaos
non-stop chaos it's just gonna start off
the episode with chaos yeah no I I feel
you man that was uh that was a whirlwind
for sure this past couple weeks so yeah
I'm very tired I feel like I need a
week-long nap
yeah we um just for context Joel and I
just got back from uh LA from the live
hacking event hacker one data h1213 and
uh we did not
we did not release an episode last week
like we were hoping to
um oops Yeah we broke our streak it's a
part of it's part of the live and learn
you know content creator life we you
have high expectations going into
something like this and uh
but yeah I mean it was really funny
because leading up to it I was like hey
aren't we supposed to record the day
that we fly to the event and you're like
yeah about that we're gonna have to
figure something out and then we're just
like ah we'll just record there with
everyone and then edit it on the spot
and post it the same night no and then
we're at the happy hour and it's like
eight o'clock at night and I walk out to
him like Hey so uh two drinks in you
know what do you want to record that
episode and you're like uh that's a
great question yeah tonight and then we
just like started grabbing hackers and
yeah that was I mean that worked out
really well though um we did grab we
grabbed quite a few quite a few great
hackers we had
we had Franz nogly Corbin Bowman
yeah Zazzle good old good old Sam Curry
himself
um so yeah no I'm glad they all came in
but we I I will I'll warn you guys
um
the audio
it's it's not great not listen
you come for the content not for the
audio okay live podcasts are a thing all
their own
um and we're figuring them out but
um if you can you know get ready to
adjust your your volume indicators and
um we tried to edit it so that it's
mostly level but yeah there are
definitely some spots that need some
love so
focus on the content for this time
around and uh we'll we'll try to we'll
try to keep the normal podcast audio as
smooth as it normally is yes absolutely
this is so this is your fair warning
turn your volume down a little bit we
have tried to normalize it but there are
definitely going to be some Peaks uh you
know these are little handheld bluetooth
mics so that's just kind of the way it
is you know so uh just uh gotta deal
with what we got and uh hopefully you
enjoy this episode because there's a lot
of really awesome stuff in there yeah
there are all right cool
um with that let's uh let's cut to the
episode you got anything else you want
to say before we Jump Right In
no I think we'll already cut it all
right peace enjoy the episode guys
okay so did you I mean did you already
do any intro stuff are we just rolling
no I just I'm we're just rolling we're
just rolling all right yeah
here here's the deal everybody
um we grabbed these little nuggly what
are you doing man yes we've been you're
good man you're good
um so we grabbed these little crappy
little mics and we grabbed a bunch of
sick Hackers from the live hacking event
that we're at in La H1 21 3 2 2 1 3 2 1
3 which is the area code for La Los
Angeles Los Angeles in case that wasn't
clear I love how we have not nagley's
literally like right here like just
right off the screen you know we've
already had enough of him uh over the
past couple episodes
um we're just gonna we're just gonna
skip everything and we're just gonna
talk about bugs today
um so everyone starts off
Corbin I don't know what I can talk
about you got it you got a bug in your
mind I mean the Transatlantic cable one
is pretty okay hit us with that you you
blogged about that though didn't you I
wrote it I
I wrote a Twitter Thread about it oh
Twitter threador
over a million views are you serious I
did yeah wow dang naturally well tell us
about that I'm gonna go tell the other
guys we're actually recording well I'll
hold this
what was it in a certain year there was
a Wikileaks document about some critical
infrastructure that the government would
not want touched okay and on that
on that document was a Transatlantic
cable called tat 14.
um I can say it now because it's
decommissioned but tap 14 was owned by a
company by the way if you work for the
government and you have a security
clearance you just violated if you are
if you work from the government turn
this off right now and you can you did
not hear anything I just said anyways
what's a translating what what's a
Wikileaks a Wiki what a Wiki what yeah
Wikipedia okay anyways yeah Wikipedia
anyways there is this bug Bounty program
that was a telecommunications company
that had this on their IP range so
um I was definitely not going out of
scope by scanning their IP ranges but I
came across a page as a web server and
on it said tat 14 and I thought it was I
mean was that was that it was it it was
like tap 14 and gave information like
this is across the Atlantic Ocean and
like just kind of some like information
Google's it I mean and looked it up I'm
like okay why the heck do they have a
marketing page for like a Transatlantic
cable like who cares like I don't even
know what that is I don't even like care
oh my gosh and I was like you know I'm
just gonna
I'm just gonna run you know like FF
against this for shits and gigs right oh
my God and all of a sudden like I'm
running it on this like really short
word list and there's a directory called
admin oh no and then it you visit the
admin and it takes you to a login page
right and so there's like ask you for
your username and password I'm like well
I don't have a username and password and
I realized it was running like tomcat
and like had like JSP
um files and so it was like posting to
like login.jsp and you tell that by
cookies
um no you just view source and it's real
hacking no okay well Tomcat you can tell
by
um like the server server header the
server header that it responds with um
but you view source and you look look at
the Forum and it's posting like a JSP
file nice so I started like doing
directory brute forcing or not like I'm
just like brute forcing for JSP files
and you know like hoping I'll be able to
just like hit a file on there and like
be able to do something unauthenticated
and there's like no results and so I
started directoring uh I start brute
forcing directories next and like
nothing really happens but I saw one was
like 301. and so I just pasted that in
my browser
um and it just redirects me to login
page but then I for some I don't even
know how it happened I think it's about
accident I'd been like I I kept
directory brute forcing and had no
success but I visited that directory
again in my browser all of a sudden I
was logged in as as an administrator to
this Transit Atlanta Cable that's crazy
so do you think that you got like a
session through like the Google search
or no so I think
um I don't even know this thing was like
super Legacy and super old but it was
like okay this directory should only be
like hit by an admin I don't know if it
was like JSP like some sort of like
Tomcat caching but when I'd hit this
directory a second time it would set a
cookie in my browser as an admin and was
there any like user account attached to
it was just like welcome no I was no I
was the admin account oh my God I go to
the users there's like there's like 30
accounts on it this Transatlantic cable
has like one like admin is the username
shared like password with like seven
people
oh no yeah and so um
I have this framed in my wall but this
is like my favorite slack conversation
to date it's like I reported to the bug
Bounty program and I knew that I knew
their technical program manager um that
was like helping that company run the
program right so I messaged him this
report I'm like I told him like what
what it was and he's like Corbin why are
you targeting
um International infrastructure critical
infrastructure like like a minute later
he just responds with holy [__]
and so I have that framed in my wall oh
my God and so I reported that to the
program and it like
it was the most underwhelming response
I've ever gotten
they said they didn't own it and it was
out of scope but it had their logo and
their name on it oh no but it was one of
those deals where it was like a
conglomerate of sure sure and nobody
nobody owns that nobody owns it because
everybody owns it right um so they fixed
it because you know nobody owns it so
nobody fixed it right
um somehow they knew about it from here
it was magical I don't know it just like
it went away it never happened wow um
but yeah that was probably one of the
funniest like most absurd bugs I've ever
found okay so takeaways from that Brute
Force stuff and pay attention to the
response right yeah there could be set
cookies in there yeah and those and you
know and actually it actually it's
pretty cool what you did because a lot
of times when you're hitting it with f
and stuff like that you're like you're
not really looking at the response you
know you're not really like in an active
browsing session yeah you're not in like
burp repeater
hit it hit the you know the end point
that you got from fuff put in your
browser pay attention to the cookies
because there could be some good
giveaways yeah there's there's a lot of
like little things like that where it's
just like you it just takes a little
like intuition and a little just like
observancy I don't know what's the word
observancy you heard it first here I
defined it observancy yeah hacker
observancy just be observant one get
intimate with the application two hacker
observancy three touch grass all right
oh gosh all right thank you Corbin that
was uh hacker underscore on Twitter
Corbin you've got um you've got
literally two words to shout something
out
oh no
he broke the rules boring mattress
company boring mattress company this man
is making
history changing sleep
mattresses
not money left you heard it here first
right FBI oh my gosh all right who's up
next
we got we got bronze Rosen we got Sam
Zazzle Curry we got Dr Bowman in the
house we got knogly yeah
that's not my middle name
nice to meet you
[Laughter]
we have to reintroduce me as the correct
all right Sam
Sam Curry the king Curry yeah
thank you all right so Sam what are you
telling us about man so we did a bunch
of car hacking recently and damn
straight one thing that was really
annoying was like Tesla is a really hard
to hack right and we got inside of a
Tesla and we sat down in it we're like
all right is this your Tesla this is my
Tesla okay yeah you know he wasn't gonna
Flex on us this was I helped him you
know wow okay
anyway so uh Tesla is like pretty
difficult to hack right we hacked all
these other car companies it was really
easy and we're like kind of mad because
we're like well we can't hack Tesla
because they're kind of harder but like
we kind of sat in there for a second
we're like all right
Tesla's have SIM cards right and the SIM
cards uh talk of course yes we're
curious we're like how does Tesla use
SIM cards so we go in the browser and I
was actually with Joel and we go in the
browser and we see that the IP address
is owned by a t that's true so we're
like okay so Tesla buys all these SIM
cards from at T
how does this work so we go to uh
business.atnt.com where you can buy SIM
cards from at T
and we're sitting there and I register
an account and I buy a SIM card so two
weeks later in the mail I get my little
SIM card it's a little device right and
I'm like looking at it and I go back to
the website and I plug it in and when
I'm plugging in I have my burp Suite
open and I kind of start fuzzing a
little bit
and I see this error when I'm buzzing it
and it says Uh there's an error in your
Jasper syntax so I'm like what's Jasper
oh that's who owns the IP range yeah so
we Google Jasper and we realized that
the entire world's telecommunication
Network for SIM cards is ran by his
company named Jasper oh my God so if
you're Verizon or at T or Bell or
whoever you basically use this company
called Jasper as a dashboard to manage
your sim cards Sam you have an uncanny
ability to find companies that run an
entire industry and then pone them well
like what what is that how do you do
that so the uh the failure on this part
was actually at T but oh really okay
yeah yeah it is a skill of mine you know
yeah
the king
but anyway so you take the secret that
you know is disclosed in this error
message from the ATT response and you
plug it into the system called Jasper
right and Jasper again is this dashboard
to manage hundreds of millions of SIM
cards right oh my God and you think you
know business at att.com you know what
am I going to have access to
so you take it and you plug it in a
dashboard and you query it and you say
search all SIM cards and it's like
results 180 million SIM cards
or something it is so oh my goodness
using this uh key that we returned from
business at att.com we plug into Jasper
and we can run a query to return
specifically Tesla SIM cards and I'm
reading the API documentation which is
this weird XML API and it has like track
location of sim card disable SIM card
send sms read SMS you know nothing too
bad yeah you know
and then we we list the customers of
business.atnt.com through another API
call we see FBI DHS NSA
so again nothing too bad no no so we're
sitting there and we realized that
through one XML API call we could
basically shut down the internet for all
Teslas or track all Teslas
and another endpoint is basically just
like read all latest text messages right
okay okay okay I'm gonna pause you here
yep so you get the token
how do you just put it into Jasper yeah
so it took uh probably two hours of
reading documentation oh man the poor
guy yeah he had to read documentation
for two hours before he popped this 183
million whatever it was well it's crazy
right because like Jasper as a
technology runs the entire world's
Telecom like if you look at any country
or any continent in the world yeah they
run 10 you know telecommunication
networks per pound that's crazy yeah
it's absurd um and these systems are
public on the internet you can go to uh
bell.jasperwireless.com if you want to
see bells and a little numeration you
can see the rest of them so remember Sam
how we said we didn't want to have to
bleep out a bunch of stuff this episode
that one out
all right cool why
why probably so we don't get a lawsuit
we just put a Target on somebody's bag
but whatever we'll figure it out
that's a crazy bug you report it okay
oh yeah so like what'd you what did they
pay you did they yeah just high fives
and you're like cool thanks by the way
that's out of scope
yeah we emailed it and reported to ATT
but we realized that they probably
weren't going to respond fast enough so
we reported through the Tesla bug
bending program since we needed a
customer and we accessed their data and
the Tesla bug money team was like
fantastic they responded within like 24
hours they fixed it or they reached out
to ATT who fixed it within like 48 Hours
wow and then it's crazy yeah Tesla
actually awarded like a bounty on att's
behalf because we were able to actually
like uh you know remotely disable any
table Tesla right so wow wow that's
crazy man thanks for thanks for dropping
that one dude that's a crazy one all
right who wants to go after that yeah
any follow-ups
what's the one up there
so you know that that was great that was
great Sam you know about the moon
all right so you know you know the moon
and where where it's at like right now
in space it wasn't always where where
it's at
it in the beginning
no so I I wanted like you can't you
can't possibly top that so
okay I'm just sitting here being
embarrassed for like the Imposter
syndrome it's hard
if there's a situation where Franz
Rosenberg every day then every day like
you know yeah I have it I have it every
day no I I I thought about it and
thought that I would probably bring it
to the angle of collaboration because I
think that's
it's such a superpower to like combine
brains in in into one and I have one bug
that that was oh sorry I speak so loudly
yeah should I erase my voice
should I take it in Swedish
you can trust me he's gonna start
cursing yeah
you don't need to like censor it you
just need to actually understand it okay
no no so so there was a fun bug where
and I think all of us have been to that
point where I found unnecessary
[Music]
and the ssrf was kind of boring like you
couldn't really like you could fetch you
know uh external things but you couldn't
hit the animata data you couldn't do
anything and you're like yeah it's a
ssrf but what the hell can I hit with
this right
um and it was like I believe it was
which is the right question by the way
yeah you know like if you have an ssrf
and you're hitting external things that
doesn't necessarily mean there's a
problem there no exactly follow the
logic of uh throws in here and think
okay what can I hit yeah yeah and and I
came to the conclusion that like I can't
really hit anything like it's it's not
really internal it's it's running on
some you know
probably like Lambda or like a cloud
function yeah exactly yeah so I couldn't
really hit anything internal
um the only the only thing that was like
different from but it's not really
different from any other but the only
thing that was different was that the
result of the ssrf was showing up inside
HTML
so you actually got HTML back inside the
content there was like rendering of the
data that you were fetching and the
content type was HTML yeah exactly so I
mean you had like a xss course but that
wasn't as fun and
and it was like super annoying uh having
that because I'm like yeah the biggest
thing you can do here is the next
success and enter Matthias of lead
imbrun Mr Matthias Carlson shout out
um I I finally got him into bug Bounty
again and I'm super happy for it is he's
back oh my God
Batman and you know you know what the
first thing is when he gets back he
writes automation so wow he was he was I
I believe I'm not gonna take any creds
for from anyone but I believe he and
shabs played with an idea very early on
pre-asset notes but the the app that
they were playing with was called asset
notes so but that's about the beta
version of it yeah exactly I remember
exactly I think they outsourced it yeah
at some point yeah
so he went away and came back now and
he's like now he's building his own
monitoring again called snooper
I made now it's it's not for sale or
anything but he's he's like he's done
he's done it again and the funny thing
this was happening at 3am in night in
the night and he's like weird idea like
what if you can do like a template
injection in the HTML from the ssrf and
I'm like yeah that sounds crazy man he's
like yeah I know whatever and we went to
sleep the day after and the day after my
kids were at home and I was like you
know they were busy with something and
I'm like yeah I'm just gonna test that
and I'm like I've never done the SSDI uh
like what what do I do he's like yeah
you can try these three ones and the
third one was like
what the hell is that he was like yeah
but it might be node so this it's like
with the you know presented sign and you
know brackets and percentage sign and
stuff yeah uh so I try that and like I
two like two times two on all of them
and like went put it on my page make
this ssrf reach that one fetch it back
in like four and I'm like
[__] you're right
you're like it's evaluating he's like oh
was it the third one yeah oh it's AGS
like EGS like yeah yeah it's just going
straight to eval
like are you sure yeah yeah he's sure
and I'm like processed that's crazy and
like get back object okay process dot
like and then I came to require it and
it's like function okay require like
shock process yeah object okay and
everything and I'm like you you [__]
crazy man thought of this idea I've
never thought about it and I'm like how
many ssrfs showing up somewhere had SSDI
and I never knew about it like I'm just
like I love that idea about like some
crazy thought about yeah what if it just
gets passed back into the template and
yeah so I love that I I think that was a
beautiful what does the code even look
like for that on this like I can't even
imagine like yeah
and then it's putting it into the
template and then rendering and then
rendering it yeah it's not even a
parameter or something it's like before
the template is even you know put into
rendering mode it's injecting that kind
of thing inside right yeah yeah
wow so so and it was just beautiful that
he he had the idea and I'm like yeah I'm
gonna try it tomorrow it wasn't even
that serious but I love that idea of
like collaborating with with those weird
thoughts because that was an a proof
that sometimes those crazy ideas can
actually be happening for real
thank you all right if we're if we're
doing template injection stuff I mean
well we talked about this one that's
right you already dropped this one right
yeah I I you know I keep on forgetting
you know whether we've talked about it
on the Pod or whether it's just chatting
yeah all right we got
oh
all right all right hit us with some
magic
also I only gave Corbin a shout out I
totally forgot to let anyone else shout
anything out so we'll do that again yeah
so what I love to do is creativities
um
um so I always try to think a little bit
out of the box and about a year ago I
was involved with some program that was
active in the music industry so I
thought like hey I might become a music
artist myself give yourself a little
hair flip there with that there you go
yeah because I want to become an artist
so I get access to certain assets I
normally don't have access to sure and
one might say hey this is social
engineering but well if you actually
create music if you actually create
artwork if you're an artist if you're a
real user of the product yeah yeah yeah
so this is this is um something that not
many people have heard but
um what I did I reached out on Fiverr we
all know Fiverr oh my God and I I got me
uh myself some Lo-Fi uh uh uh guy who
created a bead I've
um searched myself for the word book
bounty on some search engine that
indexed all the subtitles in the world
of all moves and video series so I
discovered that the A Team got a certain
moment in their in their Series where
they talk about hunting book bounties no
way so I got that phrase and put it also
on Fiverr and get a vocalist to to to uh
to make a I can say an imitation of it
yeah because I was too scared of using
the original 18 part because I thought
okay okay my music got released I might
get two I'm gonna get top of the charts
man you know so and then I had to find
someone to create yard work of course
pixel art thingy Alice in Wonderland
styles
dropped like you know 200 on this POC
like for sure actually I for this sort
of stuff I spend money so um yeah I
spend on this one I think 400 so 500.
and I want that I want those people to
earn good as well since they help me and
it's a risk and in the end if the book
works you got a good story if it does
not work you still got a good story to
share so and here we are so so this is
the the artwork cover Wonderland that
has to decide which route to go okay
yeah yeah so so there's a route without
a suit maybe we'll overlay it on the
table as like that and and
Eminem's wearing a sweater with my
initial uh domain name versus my blind
exercise thing I might have to send it
to me and
um I don't know then I ended up with
this song and and it's not being
published before and it's really hard to
find it but let me put it on yeah
[Music]
this is crazy
gotta take this and this is gonna go at
the end of the podcast yeah yeah
and there there we go because
um I released this soundtrack with all
my xss payloads as artist name as label
name because I became my own label as
well I put it at in every credit option
that was possible so I pressed this
button on uh submitting uh or publishing
or requesting review something like that
and I went to bed and the next morning I
woke up to I was blind excess reports
and I thought okay this is good but the
don't the domain name I just hit it
is a major record label and it's not
actually the third party oh and I was
like hey wait a minute of course this
this
for party on the internet where you can
publish your music on as an independent
thing is is showing the music to all the
major labels so they can discover Talent
but I popped one of their Administration
panels and I could see all the stuff of
major artists and release
you guys like yeah these major labels
are like man this one slaps guys
this is the song No but but bug bounty
sorry what my blind xss uh pops it it
steals like everything also the local
session storage is called I think yeah
and in that thing there was a big is
that a custom payload what is that no no
it's easy easy access solid yeah so you
can just speak the exercise yeah you can
just find it on GitHub install it it's
really easy and it's good
[Laughter]
I thought it was funny yeah it is no but
um the thing is that in this local
session storage was some big cheese and
blob with all the the the the music in
the queue and or being reviewed not
reviewed and with major artists there
and I was like okay I know now this rap
artist is going to release so
so I felt a little bit like ooch this is
this is hot stuff I need to report this
to the emergency record label yeah but
it was a problem it was mid-summer so
nobody was in the office nobody to reach
out to what does this mean it was what
nobody was there in the office so it was
mid-summer no I'm sorry okay wait wait
we were talking about I saw this on
Discord is this a real thing like in
Europe that like in the middle of the
summer like nobody's like we don't work
what no no no no no no it started
meanwhile in America by the end of
August people are coming back and then
on the first day of September everyone
is in the office again but talking about
our holidays and on the second week of
September you try to work
this is ridiculous meanwhile in America
we get one day a year off but imagine
it's the first of August and you just
hit this major record label and the
payload keeps popping so I got
evaporated all day I got and I had to
reach out to them and nobody picked up
the phone and at the certain moment I
finally got someone on the phone I was
like okay I want to report a security
issue with your oh no this person is not
in office you can send it to Katrina
Katrina is not acting he might well yeah
our security team's out of office for a
minute for the summer yeah
so just come back in like three months
yeah but in the middle I'll also reach
out on LinkedIn to the CEO and and
um he did not respond after two days I I
got someone to to uh help me out with
LinkedIn premium so you can push your
message a little bit more
and then I got an email back shut up
stop chasing us oh no well
and I was like okay this is not good and
also the country where this company was
uh was was headquartered is a company is
a country not not safe for ethical
hackers they're they're known for uh
well easily putting lawsuits and and
proceed and stuff so I was like
I got this beautiful song I want to
release I popped the major record label
I need them to fix the book so my son
can get published
and well after a while there's their
computer men their their CTL came back
and he reached out to me like hey this
is really cool yeah we fixed the buck
can you check check again so uh uh yeah
I checked again I did not see any new
fires so I said yeah it's it's fixed
okay now
press this approve button so I can
proceed with my research so this guy was
really helpful he pressed the approve
button so it got sent through the API
back to the asset I wasn't attacking and
it pops yeah and that was one of my best
bucks in the last year with a lot of
risks and a lot of Rough Riders I mean
we preach it all the time here on
critical thinking
pay pay the money get access to the
premium product develop your own song
[Laughter]
all right
nogly okay do you do you I mean do you
have did you already spill all your
secrets if you got something you want to
talk about all right but it's not funny
all right that's fine you know leave
that to me no but they have some funny
stuff okay cool so let's say settlement
takeovers okay you want to introduce me
no okay
this is snuggly
thank you thank you very much we're
gonna like I'm Gonna Keep I get the mic
too close and then you know we all get
them I don't want to edit this so like
keep it there you go like this yeah I
can always amplify the sound but I can't
yes you get it you get it okay let's go
okay so one funny anecdote about
supplement takeovers okay so you know I
find I'm going to take over this
occasions
with buckets every 30 seconds and then
it was like 1am some Friday night and we
don't work on a Friday night oh I think
you'll not come Friday night as well and
then I get it with the layout for a
company which is worth a couple of
billion dollars and I see hey you found
the takeover on
www.company.com actually on their own
www domain because usually those
companies they have marketing websites
yeah and this company they had like a
world with Vendo they did it and then
they messed up somehow so I just see
like okay it's 1am and I see all these
major website that a lot of users use
and it was few billion dollars Twitter
at naglin ugly this is like my essay
automatic payload holy [__] what am I
doing know like it's funny yeah everyone
navigate to the website seeing my
Twitter handle you know I think if it
was me I don't think I would have even
clicked on that alert I would have just
assumed like it was late at night I
would have just assumed ah man you know
false positive something must have
popped up yeah so it was like very very
interesting just seeing my website I've
got some DMS on Twitter so in the
morning when I woke up and they fixed it
they like eventually in the morning I
saw some games on the website developers
like the third party companies that
developed it for the client and they
said what have you done to a website why
did you do it
why did you do it we want it back oh my
gosh it was like a very very unfortunate
this poor developer went in there was
like oh I'm just gonna like change the
name on this thing for just a second and
ugly just like sniped it out from
underneath them wrecked oh my gosh
and yes I have another story
we're getting in a double not only
special yeah sorry for stealing the show
okay and so basically last year when
someone live walking event so usually I
come to life hacking events that I have
to find the crate on the on side because
the competition the pressure the turns
drafting up on the leaderboard okay I
have to put the fight so I was with
Andre there was some show they taught us
some new techniques and me and Andrew
said oh let's just play to hack the
weirdest bug level we we set ourselves a
goal we want to have authentication
bypass we want to get takeover an
arbitrary account yeah this is how a lot
of crazy bugs start too let me just say
is like you set yourself a goal like I
want to Shell on this thing or I want
auth bypass and then you just keep on
pushing and pushing and pushing until
you get it yeah yeah so basically in
this case we wanted to take over another
account all we had is like email so we
just created an email and then we try to
take over the other accounts was like
it's a public program everyone uses it
it's super hard and no one like there
are almost no bugs left on this program
so basically what we did we set our
account as admin gmail.com and then we
try the variation that he likes to use
and I also like to use it's called
ordinal indicator a what it means like
it's a very tiny a it looks like a yeah
it's a Unicode character yeah it's
Unicode but it really looks like a but
it's super small it's called ordinal
indicator on Google so what you do is we
change another email another account to
the admin with the special a.gmail.com
and when it let us change it when it
passed it like it didn't throw an L it
was a good sign at first okay we can use
this character so now our mission was to
get to all the sub domains of this
company check every SSO implementation
everything that might pass between
different Services I remember this bug
yeah and that we might like get the
authentication bypass so like I tried
four hundred sub domains I think
manually oh my God
and then like I think the last one
almost I just signing into the account
and then I said wait how did I sign in
and never registered here and it was
like very weird and then I feel sorry
from the main domain Yeah so basically
they had like their own SSO and they
said okay we know this user his admin
and then the passing between the two
applications called the like the ordinal
indicator a is the normal a and then we
just got in the application
28k dollars but no it was like very very
crazy the most creative bag of the
events
consistency and like okay we want
authentication bypass okay and you just
stick to it yeah okay so reviewing that
you you signed up on the main site you
used a Unicode character in the place of
you know for
admin.google.com then you put weird a
German yeah at google.com right yeah and
then when you single sign on to a
different thing normalize the Unicode
character and log you into admin at
google.com the actual account that we
targeted
Andre's got some crazy stuff yeah yeah
and Audrey always have amazing bugs
thank you
all right
is that it I think that's it I think
that's it what time we at we have 36
minutes oh it's perfect it's perfect
perfect all right we got we got three
minutes of uh Dr momin's song at the end
that's not too bad for an impromptu
episode
now we just have to edit it it's
currently 10 45 9 45. release is in what
so yeah lucky you saved three hours you
came to the West Coast oh my gosh
okay all right let me just let me just
uh well actually no no we'll just leave
it where I'm not even gonna try to touch
that okay we got Mr Franz Rosen which
everyone everyone already knows bronze
Rose bronze Franz you got anything you
want to shout out or anything
hello
the best we got some really like
self-serving hackers here all right
knockly wants you to watch the podcast
and tell your friends about it and post
on LinkedIn and post on LinkedIn
needs you to go to okay yeah now I'm
gonna have to make LinkedIn for this
podcast okay listen I'm not gonna check
out I'm not gonna do it now Shockwave
security yeah but I'm not gonna do it
now but nagley wants you am I gonna do
it tonight yeah Mariah says I'm gonna do
it tonight so I'm gonna go make a
LinkedIn for critical thinking tonight
and nogly in honor of nogli's amazing
double bug special yeah go give it up
what do you even do on LinkedIn you
follow go get a follow on LinkedIn yeah
follow on LinkedIn sure we got Mr uh Mr
Corbin CEO
lorbenzio laurencia Corbin Leo hacker
underscore boring
.com
the expensive domain we were not just
gonna close we got Mr Zazzle the king
Curry
oh oh he's taking his stage okay before
I shut this out I just want to say that
Ian Carol did promise me ten dollars if
I would say this
it is two words but there's a there's a
period in between it's a domain name all
right so imagine I say a period like dot
in between seats
Arrow Arrow as in the airlines oh I see
what you're saying seeds
I don't get it
seats dot arrow goes to check out
seats.arrow yep cheat said Arrow seats
down okay there we go Dr Bowman you got
a thing for us you never gave me a
referral link for that by the way
I'm sure you're watching this she's
she's always keeping track of the
leaderboard and then sharing pictures
back with me hey I saw you
hi Mom and then also also for
about like bug Bounty and what you do
bug Bounty for so why don't you share a
little bit about like what you're
passionate about in the industry okay
all right why I'm doing this actually
that's your question yeah yeah well
the thing is
um
by uh by day I work as a medical doctor
by night uh as an ethical hacker
researcher whatever group is in front of
me but
um
what I'm trying to do is learn as much
as possible to to figure out if the
stuff we use in healthcare is safe and a
lot of stuff is not safe and that's okay
if you discover it soon enough then we
can fix it and yeah there's still
mindset there like oh no we've got this
ISO thing we've got the certificate and
now it's good and now we can put this
device in the human body
and then say goodbye it's Bluetooth the
stakes get a lot higher in that scenario
you know yeah so so that's that makes me
um well a little bit passionate about
trying to figure out
what tricks are there and and and what
to do to break stuff and to show people
like hey you should fix it in my doctor
work I've got a lot of bad news
conversations like hey this is that
stuff happening in your body yeah with
ethical hacking you got the same hey
does that stop happening so there's a
lot of similarities this man is a pro at
delivering bad news
and I'm trying to combine both worlds
um so there's a lot of stuff we can
learn from medicine since the book
Bounty world is maybe 10 20 years old
it's real young medicine is well
going on for at least 1 000 years if
it's not longer
um and we managed to accelerate a lot in
the last 100 1200 years by sharing our
knowledge yeah and that's what I'm
trying to bring back a little bit to to
hacking like hey whatever you learn if
you're able to teach others share your
stories if you're company don't be
afraid that people will judge you
because you were hacked by an ethical
Hacker no people judge you by you don't
share that you were ahead exactly we got
some famous password manager that was
not sharing uh honestly what what's
going on and if they did from the start
and they showed us all the technical
details yeah we would have learned from
them and like oh whoa this is cool yeah
let us hack you again and then we might
uh be uh be there in time and not for
sure too late so yeah just a little bit
good good call Mariah having him share
that all right let's go God
vegetables Joey you guys got anything
for us on the way out
um no dude I listen uh this event is
coming up tomorrow yeah it's pretty
crazy we have a bunch of cool bugs
hopefully we'll be able to talk about
them at some point I hope so in the
meantime
we have to go edit this so yeah peace
out peace peace
I've been collecting on Bounty for 34
years now and I know what I'm doing
bug Bounty is the one I've been waiting
for all my life and I aim to see that
everything goes just right
we'll get them daddy don't you worry
well we better get them hey everybody
thanks for checking out this week's
episode of the critical thinking bug
Bounty podcast we hope you enjoyed for
more bug Benny and hacking content you
can find all of our other episodes
wherever you get your podcasts if you'd
like to watch our show in a video format
you can also find the episodes over on
our YouTube channel that's youtube.com
criticalthinkingpodcast if you have a
moment please consider leaving us a
rating or sharing this episode with your
friends and colleagues that helps a ton
and it is the best way by far to
directly support the podcast next week
we're going to have an amazing exciting
new episode coming out all about source
code review Justin and I will be talking
about all the key takeaways and
learnings that we had while prepping for
our last life hacking event and a whole
lot more you're not going to want to
miss this one see you there peace
foreign
[Music]